[
  {
    "id": "F-1",
    "question": "What is Chandler's dad's name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Charles Bing"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-2",
    "question": "What recipient name appears on Chandler and Joey's TV guide?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Miss Chanandler Bong"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-3",
    "question": "What is the name of Chandler and Ross' band that they formed in their college days?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Way, No Way"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-4",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross and Monica's childhood dog?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chi-chi"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-5",
    "question": "What was the full name of Joey's agent?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Estelle Leonard"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-6",
    "question": "During the opening credits, the letters in 'Friends' are separated by coloured dots. Name the six colours in the order they appear from left to right.",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Red, blue, yellow, red, yellow, blue"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-7",
    "question": "In season 2, Julia Roberts guest starred as an old classmate of Chandler's. After he pranked her at school, what nickname was she teased with until she was 18?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Susie Underpants"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-8",
    "question": "Which Friend's character said the first ever line in season 1, episode 1?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Monica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-9",
    "question": "Have many husbands in total have Monica, Rachel and Phoebe had?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Five husbands. Monica's only husband in the show was Chandler. Rachel had ex-fiance Barry who she ditched at the alter so he never actually became her husband but she did go on to marry Ross while drunk in Vegas. Phoebe had three husbands - Canadian ice-skater Duncan who she married so he could get a green card, Mike Hannigan, and her unnamed Vegas husband that she married in between those two marriages."
  },
  {
    "id": "F-10",
    "question": "Who was Monica's first kiss with?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-11",
    "question": "What is Joey's middle name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Francis"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-12",
    "question": "Which sister did Chandler kiss?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mary Angela"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-13",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross and Monica's grandma who died?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Althea"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-14",
    "question": "Which three savoury ingredients does Rachel include in her trifle after the recipe book pages accidentally stick together?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Beef sauteed with peas and onions"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-15",
    "question": "When Phoebe and Mike get engaged in Barbados, Mike eventually reveals that he has a girlfriend he needs to break up with back in New York. What is the name of his girlfriend?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Precious"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-16",
    "question": "What was the title of the first ever episode?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The One Where Monica Gets a Roommate"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-17",
    "question": "What was the title of the last ever episode?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The Last One"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-18",
    "question": "What song did Rachel sing at the wedding of her former best friend and ex-husband?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Copacabana"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-19",
    "question": "Finish Janice's song: 'Monica and Rachel have syrup, eh, eh, ___ _ ___ ___ __ ___ __ _____ __.'",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Now I can get my man to cheer up"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-20",
    "question": "Finish Phoebe's song: 'Oh the cow in the meadow goes moo, oh the cow in the meadow goes moo, then the farmer hits him on the head and grinds him up and _____ ___ __ ___ __________.'",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "That's how we get hamburgers"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-21",
    "question": "How long is the letter Rachel wrote Ross? (Only one specific answer will be accepted)",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "18 pages - FRONT AND BACK"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-22",
    "question": "Monica categories her towels. How many categories are there?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-23",
    "question": "What is the name of Phoebe's birth mum?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-24",
    "question": "How many sisters does Joey have?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-25",
    "question": "What soap opera does Joey star in?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Days of Our Lives"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-26",
    "question": "In the episode starring Brad Pitt, what food is Ross allergic too?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Lobster"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-27",
    "question": "Which snack to Ross and Rachel share in the first ever episode?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "An Oreo"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-28",
    "question": "What are the name of Monica and Chandler's twins?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Jack and Erica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-29",
    "question": "What number is Monica's apartment for the majority of the show?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-30",
    "question": "What is the full name of Rachel's younger assistant who she ends up dating?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Tag Jones"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-31",
    "question": "In the episode where Chandler is trying to break up with Janice, he ends up boarding a plane. Which country is the plane travelling to?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Yemen"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-32",
    "question": "Name the Friend's characters who pivoted the couch up the stairs in the famous scene?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross, Chandler and Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-33",
    "question": "At Chandler's work, a co-worker had been calling him by a different name for years and Chandler had never corrected him. What did the co-worker call Chandler?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Toby"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-34",
    "question": "What type of animal is Hugsy?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Penguin"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-35",
    "question": "Who says the last ever line on the show in the final episode?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-36",
    "question": "What is Chandler's mother's profession?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Erotic novelist"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-37",
    "question": "What is the name of Ross' girlfriend who Rachel convinces to shave her head?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Bonnie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-38",
    "question": "Which of the six main characters have worked at Central Perk?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel and Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-39",
    "question": "How much did Joey accidentally by the sail boat for?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "£20,000"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-40",
    "question": "Finish the line from the note attached to Ross' lunch that begins: 'Knock, knock. Who's there? Ross Geller's lunch. Ross Geller's lunch who?'",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross Geller's lunch, please don't take me OK?"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-41",
    "question": "What 'strip' game do the gang play at The Beach House?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Strip Happy Days Game"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-42",
    "question": "What is Danny Devito's stripper name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Officer Goodbody"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-43",
    "question": "What is Phoebe's reoccurring fake name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Regina Phalange"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-44",
    "question": "What is Chandler's dad's stage name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Helena Handbasket"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-45",
    "question": "What was the name of Chandler's crazy roommate?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Eddie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-46",
    "question": "What book does Joey read while Rachel is reading The Shining?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Little Women"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-47",
    "question": "Name all of Ross' wives in alphabetical order.",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Carol, Emily, Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-48",
    "question": "What was the giant poking device used to poke the ugly naked guy made from?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chopsticks"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-49",
    "question": "In which city the series Friends is set?",
    "choices": [
      "Los Angeles",
      "New York City",
      "Miami",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "answer": "New York City"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-50",
    "question": "What pet did Ross own?",
    "choices": [
      "A dog named Keith",
      "A rabbit called Lancelot",
      "A monkey named Marcel",
      "A lizard named Alistair"
    ],
    "answer": "A monkey named Marcel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-51",
    "question": "What is Monica most skilled at?",
    "choices": [
      "Bricklaying",
      "Cooking",
      "American football",
      "Singing"
    ],
    "answer": "Cooking"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-52",
    "question": "Monica briefly dates billionaire Pete Becker. Which country does he take her for their first date?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Italy",
      "England",
      "Greece"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-53",
    "question": "Rachel was popular in high school. Her prom date Chip ditched her for which girl at school?",
    "choices": [
      "Sally Roberts",
      "Amy Welsh",
      "Valerie Thompson",
      "Emily Foster"
    ],
    "answer": "Amy Welsh"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-54",
    "question": "What’s the name of the 1950s-themed diner where Monica worked as a waitress?",
    "choices": [
      "Marilyn & Audrey",
      "Twilight Galaxy",
      "Moondance Diner",
      "Marvin’s"
    ],
    "answer": "Moondance Diner"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-55",
    "question": "What’s the name of Joey’s penguin?",
    "choices": [
      "Snowflake",
      "Waddle",
      "Huggsy",
      "Bobber"
    ],
    "answer": "Huggsy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-56",
    "question": "Which cartoon character was on Phoebe’s thermos that Ursula threw under a bus?",
    "choices": [
      "Pebbles Flintstone",
      "Yogi Bear",
      "Judy Jetson",
      "Bullwinkle"
    ],
    "answer": "Judy Jetson"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-57",
    "question": "What’s the name of Janice’s first husband?",
    "choices": [
      "Gary Litman",
      "Sid Goralnik",
      "Rob Bailystock",
      "Nick Layster"
    ],
    "answer": "Gary Litman"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-58",
    "question": "What song is Phoebe best known for?",
    "choices": [
      "Smelly Cat",
      "Smelly Dog",
      "Smelly Rabbit",
      "Smelly Worm"
    ],
    "answer": "Smelly Cat"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-59",
    "question": "What job does Ross have?",
    "choices": [
      "Paleontologist",
      "Artist",
      "Photographer",
      "Insurance salesman"
    ],
    "answer": "Paleontologist"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-60",
    "question": "What does Joey never share?",
    "choices": [
      "His books",
      "His information",
      "His food",
      "His DVDs"
    ],
    "answer": "His food"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-61",
    "question": "What is Chandler’s middle name?",
    "choices": [
      "Muriel",
      "Jason",
      "Kim",
      "Zachary"
    ],
    "answer": "Muriel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-62",
    "question": " Which Friends character plays Dr. Drake Ramoray on the show Days Of Our Lives?",
    "choices": [
      "Ross Geller",
      "Pete Becker",
      "Eddie Menuek",
      "Joey Tribbiani"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey Tribbiani"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-63",
    "question": "What is Janice most likely to say?",
    "choices": [
      "Talk to the hand!",
      "Get me a coffee!",
      "Oh… my… God!",
      "No way!"
    ],
    "answer": "Oh… my… God!"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-64",
    "question": "What’s the name of the grumpy person who works at the coffee shop?",
    "choices": [
      "Herman",
      "Gunther",
      "Frasier",
      "Eddie"
    ],
    "answer": "Gunther"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-65",
    "question": "Who sang the Friends theme?",
    "choices": [
      "The Banksys",
      "The Rembrandts",
      "The Constables",
      "The Da Vinci Band"
    ],
    "answer": "The Rembrandts"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-66",
    "question": "What kind of uniform does Joey wear to Monica and Chandler’s wedding?",
    "choices": [
      "Chef",
      "Soldier",
      "Fire fighter",
      "A baseball player"
    ],
    "answer": "Soldier"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-67",
    "question": "What are Ross and Monica’s parents names?",
    "choices": [
      "Jack and Jill",
      "Philip and Holly",
      "Jack and Judy",
      "Margaret and Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "Jack and Judy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-68",
    "question": "What is the name of Rachel’s Sphynx cat?",
    "choices": [
      "Baldy",
      "Mrs. Whiskerson",
      "Sid",
      "Felix"
    ],
    "answer": "Mrs. Whiskerson"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-69",
    "question": "When Ross and Rachel were 'on a break,' Ross slept with Chloe. Where does she work?",
    "choices": [
      "Xerox",
      "Microsoft",
      "Domino’s",
      "Bank of America"
    ],
    "answer": "Xerox"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-70",
    "question": "What’s Chandler’s mom name?",
    "choices": [
      "Priscilla Mae Galway",
      "Nora Tyler Bing",
      "Mary Jane Blaese",
      "Jessica Grace Carter"
    ],
    "answer": "Nora Tyler Bing"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-71",
    "question": "Monica and Chandler met on Thanksgiving in 1987. She pursued her career as a chef because Chandler complimented her on which dish?",
    "choices": [
      "Green bean casserole",
      "Meatloaf",
      "Stuffing",
      "Macaroni and cheese"
    ],
    "answer": "Macaroni and cheese"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-72",
    "question": "How many seasons did the series have?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-73",
    "question": "Rachel becomes buyer assistant at which department store in season 3?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Bloomingdales"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-74",
    "question": "Monica dated one of her parents’ friends. What was his name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Richard"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-75",
    "question": "What is Richard’s job?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ophthalmologist"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-76",
    "question": "In which city did Ross and Rachel get married at the end of season 5?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Las Vegas"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-77",
    "question": "It was revealed at her memorial service that Estelle only had one other client, and he ate paper. What was his name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Al Zebooker"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-78",
    "question": "What is the name of the neighbour who lives below Monica and Rachel, often heard banging his broomstick on the ceiling?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mr. Heckles"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-79",
    "question": "Which phrase does Ross claim to have invented in ‘The One with the Mugging’?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Got Milk?"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-80",
    "question": "What is the name of the fellow paleontologist Ross dates in season 10?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Charlie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-81",
    "question": "In which city do Monica and Chandler Bing spend a night together in season 4?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-82",
    "question": "Who does Phoebe marry in season 10?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mike Hannigan"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-83",
    "question": "How many failed marriages does Ross have during the series?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-84",
    "question": "What body part does Phoebe find inside a can of soda?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A thumb"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-85",
    "question": "Who sets up Phoebe and Mike?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-86",
    "question": "What is the name of Ross’ first wife?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Carol"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-87",
    "question": "What is the nickname Monica’s dad gives her?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Little Harmonica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-88",
    "question": "What was the name of Chandler’s psycho roommate?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Eddie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-89",
    "question": "In the episode where the gang goes to Barbados, Monica and Mike play a game of ping-pong. Who scores the winning point?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mike"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-90",
    "question": "Who peed on Monica when she got stung by a jellyfish?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-91",
    "question": "What was the name of Rachel’s childhood dog?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "LaPoo"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-92",
    "question": "Who did Phoebe think her grandfather was?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Albert Einstein"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-93",
    "question": "Where did Carol first meet Susan?",
    "choices": [
      "In college",
      "At work",
      "At the gym",
      "At Central Per"
    ],
    "answer": "At the gym"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-94",
    "question": "How did Susan and Ross come up with Ben’s name?",
    "choices": [
      "It was the doctor's name",
      "They both had uncles named Ben",
      "It's the name of their favorite actor",
      "It was on the janitor's name tag"
    ],
    "answer": "It was on the janitor's name tag"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-95",
    "question": "What were Ben's first words?",
    "choices": [
      "Hi",
      "Bye",
      "Mom",
      "Dumb"
    ],
    "answer": "Hi"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-96",
    "question": "How long did Ross and Emily date before they got engaged?",
    "choices": [
      "14 days",
      "6 weeks",
      "A year",
      "3 months"
    ],
    "answer": "6 weeks"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-97",
    "question": "Rachel left Ross a drunken voicemail confessing her feelings after Ross and Julie were about to take what big relationship step?",
    "choices": [
      "Move in together",
      "Get a cat together",
      "Elope",
      "Meet Julie’s parents"
    ],
    "answer": "Get a cat together"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-98",
    "question": "What holiday did Ross and his girlfriend Mona break up on?",
    "choices": [
      "Valentine's Day",
      "Thanksgiving",
      "Christmas Day",
      "New Year's Eve"
    ],
    "answer": "Valentine's Day"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-99",
    "question": "Who did Rachel discover her ex-fiancé Barry was cheating on her with?",
    "choices": [
      "Her best friend",
      "Her sister",
      "His coworker",
      "Her college roommate"
    ],
    "answer": "Her best friend, Molly"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-100",
    "question": "What did Rachel accidentally do to Mr. Zelner during her job interview at Ralph Lauren?",
    "choices": [
      "Punch him",
      "Kiss him",
      "Rip his pants",
      "Spill coffee on him"
    ],
    "answer": "Kiss him"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-101",
    "question": "Joey and Phoebe found Tag’s sweater in Rachel’s apartment, assuming he’s her baby’s father. What color is the sweater?",
    "choices": [
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Black"
    ],
    "answer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-102",
    "question": "Rachel had a one-night stand with Paolo after Ross starts dating who?",
    "choices": [
      "Julie",
      "Mona",
      "Emily",
      "Jill"
    ],
    "answer": "Julie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-103",
    "question": "Which one of Rachel’s 'exes' came back in Season 10 to offer her a job in Paris?",
    "choices": [
      "Paul Stevens",
      "Pete Becker",
      "Richard Burke",
      "Mark Robinson"
    ],
    "answer": "Mark Robinson"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-104",
    "question": "What was Gunther’s job before he worked at Central Perk?",
    "choices": [
      "A history professor",
      "A soap opera actor",
      "A marketing executive",
      "A fashion designer"
    ],
    "answer": "A soap opera actor"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-105",
    "question": "How did Monica and Rachel convince Mr. Treeger not to kick them out for illegally subletting their apartment?",
    "choices": [
      "Rachel goes on a date with him",
      "Joey does ballroom dancing with him",
      "Monica cleans his filthy apartment",
      "Rachel and Monica bribe him with $4,000"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey does ballroom dancing with him"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-106",
    "question": "What was the name of the first restaurant Monica was head chef at?",
    "choices": [
      "Alessandro’s",
      "Moondance Diner",
      "Iridium",
      "Javu"
    ],
    "answer": "Alessandro’s"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-107",
    "question": "Monica and Chandler adopted Erica's kid(s). How many kid(s) did she have?",
    "choices": [
      "Just one",
      "Twins",
      "Triplets"
    ],
    "answer": "Twins"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-108",
    "question": "How many times did Chandler and Janice break up during the entirety of Friends?",
    "choices": [
      "Just once",
      "2 times",
      "5 times",
      "8 times"
    ],
    "answer": "5 times"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-109",
    "question": "How did Chandler finally get his bad roommate Eddie to move out?",
    "choices": [
      "He caught Eddie watching him sleep",
      "He changed the locks and pretended not to know Eddie",
      "He ate all of Eddie’s dehydrated vegetables",
      "He released a monkey in Eddie’s room"
    ],
    "answer": "He changed the locks and pretended not to know Eddie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-110",
    "question": "Chandler bought his girlfriend Kathy a first edition of her favorite childhood book for her birthday — what is it?",
    "choices": [
      "The Velveteen Rabbit",
      "The Little Prince",
      "The Giving Tree",
      "Where the Wild Things Are"
    ],
    "answer": "The Velveteen Rabbit"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-111",
    "question": "Who was briefly roommates with Australian dancer Janine Lacroix?",
    "choices": [
      "Chandler",
      "Phoebe",
      "Ross",
      "Joey"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-112",
    "question": "In “The One Where Estelle Dies,” who pretended to be Estelle when Joey called?",
    "choices": [
      "Phoebe",
      "Rachel",
      "Chandler",
      "Monica"
    ],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-113",
    "question": "Before they were friends, who did Phoebe mug as a kid?",
    "choices": [
      "Chandler",
      "Joey",
      "Monica",
      "Ross"
    ],
    "answer": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-114",
    "question": "Which one of the guys did Ursula go out with?",
    "choices": [
      "Joey",
      "Chandler",
      "Ross"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-115",
    "question": "How did Phoebe’s half-brother Frank meet his fiancé Alice?",
    "choices": [
      "She was his favorite grocery store clerk",
      "She was his teacher",
      "She was his ER nurse",
      "She was his coworkers mom"
    ],
    "answer": "She was his teacher"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-116",
    "question": "Name Alice and Frank Jr.’s kids?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Leslie, Chandler & Frank Jr. Jr."
  },
  {
    "id": "F-117",
    "question": "How did Phoebe meet her boyfriend Gary? ",
    "choices": [
      "He was a massage client",
      "He left her a large tip at Central Perk",
      "She tried to trick him into thinking she was a cop",
      "She and Monica catered his divorce party"
    ],
    "answer": "She tried to trick him into thinking she was a cop"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-118",
    "question": "Phoebe’s love interest David couldn’t be with her because he had a grant to study where?",
    "choices": [
      "Yemen",
      "Minsk",
      "Aruba",
      "Athens"
    ],
    "answer": "Minsk"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-119",
    "question": "How did Mike Hannigan originally want to propose to Phoebe?",
    "choices": [
      "During a performance at Central Perk",
      "At a Knicks game",
      "On New Year's Eve in Times Square",
      "By pretending to be a massage client"
    ],
    "answer": "At a Knicks game"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-120",
    "question": "Jasmine knew about Ross cheating on Rachel because Isaac from the Xerox store is her brother. Who did she tell?",
    "choices": [
      "Her coworker, Phoebe",
      "Her ex-boyfriend, Joey",
      "Her friend and Rachel's coworker, Tag",
      "Her roommate, Gunther"
    ],
    "answer": "Her roommate, Gunther"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-121",
    "question": "Who had a crush on Joshua Burgin?",
    "choices": [
      "Monica",
      "Rachel",
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-122",
    "question": "Who did Charlie Wheeler date?",
    "choices": [
      "Chandler and Joey",
      "Joey and Ross",
      "Chandler and Ross",
      "Chandler, Joey, and Ross"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey and Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-123",
    "question": "Dr. Long appeared in 5 episodes of Friends as Rachel’s obstetrician during which season?",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-124",
    "question": "What is the name of Ross's student and ex-girlfriend?",
    "choices": [
      "Sarah",
      "Elizabeth",
      "Amanda",
      "Samantha"
    ],
    "answer": "Elizabeth"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-125",
    "question": "Who got hit with a tranquilizer dart while trying to save Ross's monkey Marcel?",
    "choices": [
      "Rachel",
      "Monica",
      "Joey",
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-126",
    "question": "Which one of Rachel’s sisters was played by Reese Witherspoon?",
    "choices": [
      "Amy",
      "Jill"
    ],
    "answer": "Jill"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-127",
    "question": "What did Rachel and her other sister, Amy, fight about on Thanksgiving?",
    "choices": [
      "Who would get Emma if Rachel and Ross die",
      "Which sister stole the other’s boyfriend in college",
      "Who is actually mom's favorite child",
      "Who inherits dad's house"
    ],
    "answer": "Who would get Emma if Rachel and Ross die"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-128",
    "question": "What does Monica's dad, Jack, give her because her childhood belongings were ruined in a flood?",
    "choices": [
      "Their childhood home",
      "Her own restaurant",
      "His Porsche",
      "$10,000"
    ],
    "answer": "His Porsche"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-129",
    "question": "Which member of the Friends crew kissed Rachel’s mom?",
    "choices": [
      "Chandler",
      "Ross",
      "Phoebe",
      "Joey"
    ],
    "answer": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-130",
    "question": "What job did Rachel's dad have?",
    "choices": [
      "Professor",
      "Attorney",
      "Doctor",
      "TV personality"
    ],
    "answer": "Doctor"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-131",
    "question": "What is the name of Phoebe's actual birth mother?",
    "choices": [
      "Phoebe",
      "Gloria",
      "Meredith",
      "Sky"
    ],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-132",
    "question": "Which one of Joey's sisters accidentally got pregnant in Season 8?",
    "choices": [
      "Gina",
      "Mary-Therese",
      "Dina",
      "Mary-Angela"
    ],
    "answer": "Dina"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-133",
    "question": "What store does Phoebe hate?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Pottery Barn"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-134",
    "question": "Rachel got a job with which company in Paris?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-135",
    "question": "What was the occupation of Rachel’s fiancé Barry Farber?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Orthodontist"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-136",
    "question": "Who was the maid of honor at Monica’s wedding?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-137",
    "question": "Which Sprouse brother played Ross’ son Ben?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Cole"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-138",
    "question": "True or false, Rachel kissed all of her Friends (male and female) on the show?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-139",
    "question": "What is the name of Phoebe’s twin sister?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ursula"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-140",
    "question": "Ross says whose name at the altar in London?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-141",
    "question": "Which member of the British royal family appeared on Friends?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Sarah Ferguson/Duchess of York"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-142",
    "question": "Brad Pitt and David Schwimmer’s characters cofounded what club in high school?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The 'I Hate Rachel Green Club.'"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-143",
    "question": "Which of Joey’s sisters did Chandler fool around with?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mary Angela"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-144",
    "question": "Who was Joey’s imaginary childhood friend? ",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Maurice"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-145",
    "question": "What was the profession of Joey’s imaginary friend?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Space cowboy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-146",
    "question": "What was Monica’s nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Big Fat Goalie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-147",
    "question": "What does Rachel guess Chandler’s job is?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A transponster"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-148",
    "question": "What is Richard’s daughter’s name?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Michelle"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-149",
    "question": "Who mistakingly threw a woman’s wooden leg into a fire?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-150",
    "question": "Ross and Rachel’s wedding dinner was held where in Vegas?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A Pizza Hut"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-151",
    "question": "According to Monica, a woman has how many erogenous zones?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-152",
    "question": "What does Phoebe legally change her name to after her wedding?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Princess Consulea Banana Hammock"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-153",
    "question": "What form of self-defense does Ross try to teach Rachel and Phoebe?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Unagi"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-154",
    "question": "What song makes Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma laugh for the first time?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Sir Mix-a-Lot’s 'Baby Got Back.'"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-155",
    "question": "What caused the fire at Rachel and Phoebe’s apartment?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel’s hair straightener"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-156",
    "question": "What color is Monica’s apartment?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Purple"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-157",
    "question": "Ross’ first wife Carol leaves him for who?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Susan Bunch"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-158",
    "question": "What is the name of Chandler’s father’s Las Vegas all-male burlesque?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Viva Las Gaygas"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-159",
    "question": "Phoebe attempts to teach Joey what language?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "French"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-160",
    "question": "Chick Jr. and Duck Jr. got stuck in what?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A foosball table"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-161",
    "question": "Who was married to a supposedly gay Canadian ice dancer named Duncan?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-162",
    "question": "Rachel was in which sorority?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Kappa Kappa Delta"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-163",
    "question": "What are the names of Rachel’s sisters?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Jill and Amy Greene"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-164",
    "question": "Which character famously said, “PIVOT?”",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-165",
    "question": "Rachel goes on Ross’ honeymoon by herself where?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Athens, Greece"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-166",
    "question": "What holiday does Chandler hate?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-167",
    "question": "Who was Rachel’s prom date?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chip Matthews"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-168",
    "question": "What actor played Phoebe’s husband Mike Hannigan?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Paul Rudd"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-169",
    "question": "Where did Ross and Rachel have their first date?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The planetarium"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-170",
    "question": "How many roses did Ross send Emily?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-171",
    "question": "What year did Friends first premiere?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-172",
    "question": "Joey’s Cabbage Patch Kid is named what?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Alicia May Emor"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-173",
    "question": "What was the name of the game Chandler made up to give Joey money?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Cups"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-174",
    "question": "In an effort to get over Richard, Monica started making what?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Jam"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-175",
    "question": "What fruit is Ross allergic to?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Kiwi"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-176",
    "question": "What is Rachel’s favorite flower?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Lillies"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-177",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross and Rachel’s male nanny?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Sandy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-178",
    "question": "Who came on to who in The One With The Videotape?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel came on to Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-179",
    "question": "What was Joey’s nickname when he was working at Alessandro’s?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Dragon"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-180",
    "question": "What was Rachel’s bra size?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "32C"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-181",
    "question": "Ross worked as a professor at what school?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "New York University"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-182",
    "question": "What word did Rachel misspell on her resume?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Computer"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-183",
    "question": "Who said, 'See, he’s her lobster!'",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-184",
    "question": "What is the first wedding gift Monica opens?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A tiny salt shaker"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-185",
    "question": "Rachel’s sister Amy decides she wants to become what after babysitting Emma?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A baby stylist"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-186",
    "question": "Ross and Carol were busted having sex on which Disney ride?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "It’s a Small World"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-187",
    "question": "Which Friend entered a Vanilla Ice lookalike contest and won?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-188",
    "question": "Phoebe thought “Kenny the Copy Guy” was who?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ralph Lauren"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-189",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey’s barcalounger?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rosita"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-190",
    "question": "Monica could not tell time until what age?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-191",
    "question": "Phoebe created a three-dimensional picture of a woman named?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Gladys"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-192",
    "question": "Who was the last Friend to find out about Monica and Chandler’s relationship?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-193",
    "question": "Chandler and Joey both dated an actress named?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Kathy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-194",
    "question": "What did Monica want from Phoebe as an engagement present?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Her grandmother‘s cookie recipe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-195",
    "question": "Who had a pony and a boat at age 15?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-196",
    "question": "Phoebe said something was wrong with the right or the left phalange of Rachel’s plane?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The left"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-197",
    "question": "Who is Santa’s friend that Ross invents to teach Ben about Hanukkah?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The Holiday Armadillo"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-198",
    "question": "Who is the youngest Friend?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-199",
    "question": "Chandler told Janice he was moving where to avoid seeing her again?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Yemen"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-200",
    "question": "Phoebe’s grandmother said she got her cookie recipe from her grandmother named?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Nestle Toulouse (AKA Nestlé Toll House)"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-201",
    "question": "The Geller Cup was a trophy for which sport?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Touch football games"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-202",
    "question": "Who did Monica forget to invite to Rachel’s baby shower?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel’s mother Sandra"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-203",
    "question": "Which of Monica’s boyfriends wanted to become the Ultimate Fighting Champion?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Pete (Peter Becker)"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-204",
    "question": "What was the name of the lipstick brand for men that Joey starred in a Japanese commercial for?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ichiban"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-205",
    "question": "Ross, Susan and Phoebe got stuck where before Ben’s birth?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A closet"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-206",
    "question": "Who gave Phoebe away at her wedding?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-207",
    "question": "Monica and Chandler first got together where?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-208",
    "question": "The handcuffs that were found in Rachel’s former room belonged to who?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Monica and Ross’ Nana (grandmother)"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-209",
    "question": "Chandler and Ross helped Joey practice for what game show audition?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Bamboozled"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-210",
    "question": "What does Chandler call the Paris of Oklahoma?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Tulsa"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-211",
    "question": "What food caused Ross to get sick on Space Mountain?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Tacos"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-212",
    "question": "Who is older: Ross or Monica?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-213",
    "question": "What is actually Rachel’s favorite movie?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Weekend at Bernie’s"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-214",
    "question": "Which Friend had a traumatic swing incident at age 4?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-215",
    "question": "Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma would have turned 18 what year?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "2020"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-216",
    "question": "Which Friend didn’t go to London for Ross’ wedding?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-217",
    "question": "What kind of bed did the Mattress King deliver to Monica?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A racecar bed"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-218",
    "question": "Emma’s first birthday cake was supposed to be shaped like what?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A bunny"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-219",
    "question": "In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Her ear"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-220",
    "question": "Ross created a comic book called what?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Science Boy"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-221",
    "question": "What is Joey’s favorite food?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Sandwiches"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-222",
    "question": "How old was Chandler when he first touched a girl’s breast?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-223",
    "question": "Which Friend had his/her identity stolen?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Monica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-224",
    "question": "Joey doesn’t read which book without making sure there is plenty of room in the freezer?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "The Shining"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-225",
    "question": "Who stole all the insoles out of Chandler’s shoes?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler’s roomate Eddie"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-226",
    "question": "Who gave Rachel and Ross the name “Emma” for their daughter?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Monica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-227",
    "question": "Joey was cast as the butt double for which actor?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Al Pacino"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-228",
    "question": "What year did the series finale of Friends air?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "2004"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-229",
    "question": "What is the name of Rachel and Monica’s building superintendent?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mr. Treeger"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-230",
    "question": "What is Joey’s pin number?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "5639"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-231",
    "question": "What was the last state that Ross couldn’t remember?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Delaware"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-232",
    "question": "What was the name of Chandler’s roommate prior to Joey?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Kip"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-233",
    "question": "Whose idea was it to get married in Vegas, Rachel or Ross’?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-234",
    "question": "What was the name of Monica’s imaginary boyfriend?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Jared"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-235",
    "question": "What kind of plastic surgery did Rachel have?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A nose job"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-236",
    "question": "Who was called Sir Limps-a-Lot after losing a toe?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-237",
    "question": "Which balloon got away during the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade in Season 1?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Underdog"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-238",
    "question": "Who gave birth to Chandler and Monica’s twins?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Erica"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-239",
    "question": "Chandler and Rachel ate cheesecake off the floor from what bakery?  ",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mama’s Little Bakery"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-240",
    "question": "Monica, Ross and Rachel attended what high school?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Lincoln High School"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-241",
    "question": "Who were on “a break”?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Rachel and Ross"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-242",
    "question": "What was the name of Monica’s senior prom date?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Roy Gublik"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-243",
    "question": "Ross was jealous of who at Rachel’s job?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Mark"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-244",
    "question": "What was the name of the 'hot girl from the Xerox place?'",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "Chloe"
  },
  {
    "id": "F-245",
    "question": "What did Rachel get a tattoo of?",
    "choices": [],
    "answer": "A heart"
  }
]